<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Link-Rot</title>
    <description>Link Rot is a show about the intersection of life and technology. Each week we dive into a subject that explores changes in digital technology and the way it affects our lives. We discuss how technology impacts our very humanity and have fun along the way!</description>
    <link>/link-rot/</link>
    <atom:link href="/link-rot/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 14:44:31 +1000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 14:44:31 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will Netflix kill TV?</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;will-netflix-kill-tv&quot;&gt;Will Netflix kill TV?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The power of TV has been dwindling over recent years. It is no longer something that unites a nation, it’s not something we do as a collective anymore. Timeshifting, VCRs, DVRs and streaming make watching on demand possible and, by handing us the remote, perhaps a more desirable experience. Netflix’s arrival to Australian shores has had a massive effect on our viewing habits - and the experience of Netflix is fundamentally different to TV. It’s on demand, all available, ad free and cheap - so will it kill TV?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;links&quot;&gt;Links:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/hPD_RHVFlys&quot;&gt;Agro’s Cartoon Connection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 20:37:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>/link-rot/2016/episode-3.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/link-rot/2016/episode-3.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Physicality of Stuff</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-happens-when-we-lose-the-physicality-of-stuff&quot;&gt;What happens when we lose the physicality of “stuff”?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More and more of our lives are becoming digitised - digital objects without a physical equivalent or presence. Shelves of CDs are replaced by Spotify subscriptions, DVDs by Netflix, Photo albums are relics of the past. So what kind of effect does this have on us - our identity and how we navigate our history?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;voices&quot;&gt;Voices&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Klapdor, Ben Atkinson and Adam Webster&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 20:37:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>/link-rot/2016/episode-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/link-rot/2016/episode-2.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boring iPhones &amp; Digital Death</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;just-how-boring-is-the-iphone&quot;&gt;Just how boring is the iPhone?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We discuss just how boring is Apple? Why is there this expectation around innovation? Is the same expectation placed on Samsung, Microsoft and Google? What’s the last bit of tech that actually made you excited? And &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; tech actually make you excited or are our lives just that sad?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://daringfireball.net/&quot;&gt;Daring Fireball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-does-dying-look-like-today&quot;&gt;What does dying look like today?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In todays digital age what exactly does death look like today? Should we build computers that forget? Could we set timelines for data to die or fade? What happens when an algorithm has access to our memories? Is somones social media page a memorial or does it stop us from moving on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://motherboard.vice.com/read/how-digital-possessions-keep-us-from-letting-go-of-the-dead&quot;&gt;We Need to Make Digital Data That Dies Like Us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meyerweb.com/eric/thoughts/2014/12/24/inadvertent-algorithmic-cruelty/&quot;&gt;Inadvertent Algorithmic Cruelty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/15rb1k/a_medicalert_bracelet_like_this_might_be_sensible/&quot;&gt;Please delete my browser history&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 14:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>/link-rot/2016/episode-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/link-rot/2016/episode-1.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
